<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Agenda on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/</link><description>Recent content in Agenda on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Closing words</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/closing_words/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:50:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/closing_words/</guid><description>Closing words</description></item><item><title>Cyber Cold War by Proxy: Saudi vs. Iran</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Cold War in the Middle East, Iran vs. Saudi Arabia &amp;amp; the entire region. The year 2012 almost crashed every world economy, threatening to bring the modern world to an end with the first Shamoon attacks by Iran. Since then, Iran has launched devastating cyber attacks against its perceived enemies involving critical infrastructure, to manipulate the oil markets in its favor. Join Chris on a journey of fighting near constant Cyberwar attacks and counter attacks!</description></item><item><title>CTF announcement</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/ctf_announcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:40:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/ctf_announcement/</guid><description>CTF announcement</description></item><item><title>Community Talk: Volunteering during crisis - The CTI League</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/community_talk__volunteering_during_crisis__-_the_cti_league/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:20:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/community_talk__volunteering_during_crisis__-_the_cti_league/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Volunteering during crisis - CTI League, a global threat intelligence experts community that neutralize cyber threats exploiting the current COVID-19 pandemic&amp;rdquo;. In the last months, a global army of 1800 cyber threat intelligence volunteers has been fighting threat actors looking to exploit the COVID-19 pandemic. The Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) League is the first community and global CERT in the world, established for helping the medical sector in its most sensitive time.</description></item><item><title>Break #3</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:10:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#3/</guid><description>10 minutes break - please visit our sponsors! https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/</description></item><item><title>Yoga Break with Emily</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/yoga_break_with_emily/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:55:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/yoga_break_with_emily/</guid><description>Stretch out and enjoy a short yoga practice with Emily Shain. Some easy yoga moves everyone can do at home! http://www.yogawemily.com/</description></item><item><title>Free Blue-Team TTPs: Stop Shiny Object Syndrome</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue-team_ttps_stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:10:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue-team_ttps_stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</guid><description>Too many blue-teamers get dazzled by hype for fancy new tools, especially those that are new to the industry. What they don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that there are free or cheap Tools, Tactics and Procedures that can shore up defenses today, without having to buy something new.</description></item><item><title>The Art of C2: Myths vs. Reality</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/the_art_of_c2_myths_vs._reality/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:55:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/the_art_of_c2_myths_vs._reality/</guid><description>“You need a TCP/IP connection for a C’n’C Server”, don&amp;rsquo;t you?? a dynamic, real-time Command and Control is not about an established connection. Nor TCP. or UDP. It’s a MINDSET :) We&amp;rsquo;ll show you some cool demos from our research and tools we wrote for our creative assessments, demonstrating C&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;C &amp;ldquo;living of the land&amp;rdquo; with your email client, Bluetooth with text messages, SSIDs and even dropped packets ;-)</description></item><item><title>Eliminating Alert Fatigue: Reducing False Positives Through Better Engineering</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</guid><description>False Positive alerts are the bane of blue teams everywhere. Countless hours are lost as Security Operation Center analysts attempt to separate the wheat from the alert chaff to find the real indicators of an attack. Reducing FPs is thus a critical goal for any security platform. Yet reducing FPs at the expense of missing the signs of an actual threat is inviting disaster. The solution to this conundrum lies in better engineering: building the right tools to accurately assess alerts at scale.</description></item><item><title>Break #2</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:15:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#2/</guid><description>10 minutes break</description></item><item><title>Shatter Reloaded: Reviving shatter attacks to escape sandboxes and evade endpoint security products</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</guid><description>Shatter attacks were all the rage in 2003 but were quickly neutralized by DEP, UIPI and Session 0 isolation. 15 years later, confronted with a commercial sandbox and with state-of-the-art endpoint security products – we brought Shatter attacks back to life, extending and weaponizing them to be useful once more. In this talk, we’ll present a novel code injection technique that uses an enhanced shatter attack to stealthily inject code into window explorer on Win7 &amp;amp; Win10.</description></item><item><title>Now You TCP Me, Now You Don't: The Strengths and Weaknesses of Various Internet Scanning Services</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</guid><description>A wild router is connected to the web! Are Shodan and Censys the only ones who index it? Absolutely not! They are only two of the many internet scanning services that let users interact with port scanning data they routinely collect. Although their names are well-known, details about them, the data they gather, and how best to use them are more word-of-mouth than common knowledge. I will explore these and other lesser-known websites, and help security researchers understand their strengths.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Break</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</guid><description>Lunch break</description></item><item><title>Panel - 'Security Careers in the Corona Age'</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel_-_security_careers_in_the_corona_age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:05:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel_-_security_careers_in_the_corona_age/</guid><description>How has the world of work changed for security pros? What is the Covid Effect on jobs in our industry? Is now the time to go Freelance or Corp? How are community organizations like BSidesTLV, OWASP and Cyber Ladies helping out? These are some of the questions we will explore in this fun, fast paced panel!</description></item><item><title>Regipy: Automating registry forensics with python</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:35:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</guid><description>Regipy is an OS independent python library for parsing offline registry hives. Regipy can be used to parse registry hives in scale (collected from hundreds of machines) and a lot of interesting data analysis can be done on the results, as I intend to show in the Demo. The demo would be very practical and show how the results of Regipy can be useful to crack a forensic case. (See a small example in the blog post attached)</description></item><item><title>Break #1</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break_#1/</guid><description>10 minutes break</description></item><item><title>ROP - From Zero to Nation State In 25 Minutes</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</guid><description>“The only interesting answers are those which destroy the questions.” ― Susan Sontag
Roll up your sleeves and prepare for hands on demonstration of transforming a simple process injection into a new improved version of Stack Bombing that will evade most detection tools.
We will focus on building a ROP and take a &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; approach to process injection, continuously improving the same code to evade detection and mitigation techniques.</description></item><item><title>WhoAmI, anyway?</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami_anyway/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami_anyway/</guid><description>All InfoSec challenges today may be traced back to the design mindset of the Internet Protocol Suite in the late 60&amp;rsquo;s &amp;amp; early 70&amp;rsquo;s: non-repudiation, confidentiality, spoofing etc’ were Not in the design goals of TCP/IP. Decades after, we’re creatively &amp;amp; immensely manipulating time &amp;amp; space over the internet. Malware uses deception to evade defenses, defenders use deception to deter adversaries. Attribution of actions to entities becomes challenging than ever. So WhoAreWe, anyway?</description></item><item><title>Opening Words: BSidesTLV 2020 - Welcome to the New Normal!</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/opening_words_bsidestlv_2020__-_welcome_to_the_new_normal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/opening_words_bsidestlv_2020__-_welcome_to_the_new_normal/</guid><description>Opening Words: BSidesTLV 2020 - Welcome to the New Normal!</description></item></channel></rss>