<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2020 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2020/</guid><description>Last update: 13-Jun-2020
Rules and Guidelines Remote participation is allowed (for all teams) this year In the past, we only allowed physically present teams to claim a prize, we are considering a different approach this year This is a game, play fairly - we reserve the right to disqualify participants (and we came pretty close to do that in the past) Register to the competition at ctf20.bsidestlv.com, you must be registered to participate Each team may be made of one or more individuals You&amp;rsquo;re invited to join our Slack channel</description></item><item><title>The BSidesTLV 2020 Call for Papers</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</guid><description>The 2020 edition of Security BSides in Israel, BSidesTLV 2020, will take place once again during Tel Aviv University’s Cyber Week, on Thursday, July 2.
BSidesTLV is a hands-on, community-organized hacking and security research event. This is the chance for you to share knowledge, ideas and demonstrate what you’ve been up to!
We encourage talk submissions by both newbies and veterans, from people passionate about security from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>2019 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2019/</guid><description>Hall of Fame 1st Place 2nd Place 3rd Place Honorable mention, again :-) Dan (dm0n) JCTF YaakovCohen88
Schtrudel
Narcissus
Moshe Wagner
Israel Erlich
Dvd848 EY (3rN357&amp;amp;Y0un9) Adam D Our Team Reut Menashe Roei Sherman Nimrod Levy El Profesor (w/Nimrod)</description></item><item><title>Hiring Ground</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</guid><description>BSidesTLV 2019 Hiring Ground - 24.6 10:00-16:00 This is the first year we are doing our BSidesTLV “Hiring Ground”. We are doing our best to have a wonderful event, but please make allowances for any mistakes we might make. Our hope is that this part of the event will be focused on helping members of our community find their next positions, and connect them with potential employers.
Agenda The hiring ground will operate at the 24.</description></item><item><title>2018 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2018/</guid><description>Hall of Fame 1st Place 2nd Place 3rd Place Honorable mention reclass (Nir Lavi and Intel’s team) babyr00t (known also as dm0n) JCTF (@schturdel, @nmontag, @YaakovCohen88 and Israel Erlich) Adam Donenfeld One of our volunteers was kind enough to deliver a care package to Adam Donenfeld – while not eligible to win, he did solve everything first.</description></item><item><title>2016 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2016/</guid><description>At the 2016 CTF was hosted and sponsored by Cellebrite
github: cool story bro
if you have any writeups or more information, please let me know!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben-israel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben-israel/</guid><description>Even before she first logged on to a router, Adi has loved the internet. And after she found routers and smart devices she realized the power that non-end-devices held. Since then, she&amp;rsquo;s searched the web for interesting phenomena using all available resources. With five years of experience, she hopes to share some of her knowledge and help the cybersecurity community utilize the tools available to them.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</guid><description>Chris Kubecka is the founder and CEO of HypaSec offering nation-state incident management, ethical hacking training in IT, IOT, ICS SCADA and expert advisory services to governments. Prior to HypaSec, she headed the Information Protection Group and international intelligence for the Aramco family. Re-establishing international business operations, helping to stabilize the oil market and implementing digital security after the company suffered from the world’s most devastating Shamoon cyberwarfare attacks which wiped out 85% of computer systems which deeply affected the countries of Saudi Arabia, Qatar and Bahrain.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</guid><description>Dana leads Security Research for Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft, researching and developing new cyber security threat detections. She started her career in an elite Israeli military cyber intelligence unit (&amp;lsquo;8200&amp;rsquo;), proceeded to work at a Big Data startup, and then joined Google, in its Zurich HQ. For the past 5 years she has been working on Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft. Dana is passionate about Operating Systems and Windows Internals.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</guid><description>Co-Founder of 10root Cyber security</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</guid><description>Gil Fidel is the Head of R&amp;amp;D at Accenture Security Israel (Maglan), with a long track of cutting-edge Research and Engineering in the fields of cyber security, windows internals, A/V streaming, network security &amp;amp; encryption, virtualization and AI/ML.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart-magen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart-magen/</guid><description>null</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</guid><description>null</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g._korman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g._korman/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on the R&amp;amp;D team in Sygnia, working on new tools for the IR analysts in the company. Prior to that I worked in an incident response position in Sygnia for two years. Before joining Sygnia I worked at IBM&amp;rsquo;s Trusteer as a malware researcher reversing &amp;amp; analyzing financial malware. I did military service in the software division of the IAF (Israeli Airforce) for 6 years in multiple DFIR &amp;amp; IT positions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</guid><description>Omer is End-Point team lead at Symantec (formerly Javelin Networks). His team focuses on methods to covertly manipulate OS internals. Before Symantec he was a malware researcher at IBM Trusteer for two years focusing on financial malware families. In the past he has worked at Algotec for six years developing medical imaging software and at IDF&amp;rsquo;s technology unit for three years as dev team lead. Omer lectured on DEF CON, DerbyCon, Virus Bulletin and Zero Nights conferences.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</guid><description>Y1nTh35h3ll, InfoSec Researcher, White ^ haכk3r @ 10Root. Founder of the Oriental Rock Orchestra. P0w3r5h3ll dude. mother of Bouzoukitara (musical instrument). AD Protector. detailed: Since the early 1990s, accumulated extensive experience in information security, adversary simulations/Red-Blue team training, conducting internal investigations and more. Worked for Microsoft ~8 years as Technology Group Manager and coded support tools for Windows Server. Advisory board @ Javelin Networks (sold to Symantec in 2018). Spoke at TED and TEDx events, and was awarded 4 Peace and friendship awards by cities and governments around the world.</description></item><item><title>AppsFlyer</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/appsflyer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/appsflyer/</guid><description>Check out AppsFlyer @ https://www.appsflyer.com/</description></item><item><title>Check Point</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/checkpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/checkpoint/</guid><description>Check out Check Point @ https://www.checkpoint.com/</description></item><item><title>Clear Sky</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/clearsky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/clearsky/</guid><description>Check out Clear Sky @ https://www.clearskysec.com/</description></item><item><title>Closing words</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/closing_words/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/closing_words/</guid><description>Closing words</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>All attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at our conference are required to agree with the following code of conduct. Organizers will enforce this code throughout the event. We expect cooperation from all participants to help ensure a safe environment for everybody.
BSidesTLV is dedicated to providing a safe and harassment-free conference experience regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices, to all participants.</description></item><item><title>CTF announcement</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/ctf_announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/ctf_announcement/</guid><description>CTF announcement</description></item><item><title>Cyber Cold War by Proxy: Saudi vs. Iran</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Cold War in the Middle East, Iran vs. Saudi Arabia &amp;amp; the entire region. The year 2012 almost crashed every world economy, threatening to bring the modern world to an end with the first Shamoon attacks by Iran. Since nearly bring the world to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, Iran has launched devastating cyber attacks against it&amp;rsquo;s perceived enemies involving critical infrastructure, to manipulate the oil markets in its favor.</description></item><item><title>Cybereason</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cybereason/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cybereason/</guid><description>Check out Cybereason @ https://www.cybereason.com/</description></item><item><title>Eliminating Alert Fatigue: Reducing False Positives Through Better Engineering</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</guid><description>False Positive alerts are the bane of blue teams everywhere. Countless hours are lost as Security Operation Center analysts attempt to separate the wheat from the alert chaff to find the real indicators of an attack. Reducing FPs is thus a critical goal for any security platform. Yet reducing FPs at the expense of missing the signs of an actual threat is inviting disaster. The solution to this conundrum lies in better engineering: building the right tools to accurately assess alerts at scale.</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/faq/</guid><description>FAQs What is Security BSides, anyway? Started by a group of hackers, security researchers and people passionate about cyber security, who are keen to share their knowledge and ideas, Security Bsides is a global network of community oriented, grassroots non-profit security events taking place anywhere from Athens, to São Paulo!
From the Bsides Community Wiki: “Bsides creates opportunities for individuals to both present and participate in an intimate atmosphere that encourages collaboration.</description></item><item><title>HackerOne</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/hackerone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/hackerone/</guid><description>Check out HackerOne @ https://hackerone.com/sign_up</description></item><item><title>Intel</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/intel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/intel/</guid><description>Check out Intel @ https://www.intel.co.il/content/www/il/he/homepage.html</description></item><item><title>Neuralegion</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/neuralegion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/neuralegion/</guid><description>Check out Neuralegion @ https://go.neuralegion.com/bsidestlv</description></item><item><title>Now You TCP Me, Now You Don't: The Strengths and Weaknesses of Various Internet Scanning Services</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</guid><description>A wild router is connected to the web! Are Shodan and Censys the only ones who index it? Absolutely not! They are only two of the many internet scanning services that let users interact with port scanning data they routinely collect. Although their names are well-known, details about them, the data they gather, and how best to use them are more word-of-mouth than common knowledge. I will explore these and other lesser-known websites, and help security researchers understand their strengths.</description></item><item><title>Opening words</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/opening_words/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/opening_words/</guid><description>Opening words</description></item><item><title>Regipy: Automating registry forensics with python</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</guid><description>Regipy is an OS independent python library for parsing offline registry hives. Regipy can be used to parse registry hives in scale (collected from hundreds of machines) and a lot of interesting data analysis can be done on the results, as I intend to show in the Demo. The demo would be very practical and show how the results of Regipy can be useful to crack a forensic case. (See a small example in the blog post attached)</description></item><item><title>ROP - From Zero to Nation State In 25 Minutes</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</guid><description>“The only interesting answers are those which destroy the questions.” ― Susan Sontag
Roll up your sleeves and prepare for hands on demonstration of transforming a simple process injection into a new improved version of Stack Bombing that will evade most detection tools.
We will focus on building a ROP and take a &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; approach to process injection, continuously improving the same code to evade detection and mitigation techniques.</description></item><item><title>Shatter Reloaded: Reviving shatter attacks to escape sandboxes and evade endpoint security products</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</guid><description>Shatter attacks were all the rage in 2003 but were quickly neutralized by DEP, UIPI and Session 0 isolation. 15 years later, confronted with a commercial sandbox and with state-of-the-art endpoint security products – we brought Shatter attacks back to life, extending and weaponizing them to be useful once more. In this talk, we’ll present a novel code injection technique that uses an enhanced shatter attack to stealthily inject code into window explorer on Win7 &amp;amp; Win10.</description></item><item><title>The Art of C2: Myths vs. Reality</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/the_art_of_c2_myths_vs._reality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sessions/the_art_of_c2_myths_vs._reality/</guid><description>“You need a TCP/IP connection for a C’n’C Server”, don&amp;rsquo;t you?? a dynamic, real-time Command and Control is not about an established connection. Nor TCP. or UDP. It’s a MINDSET :) We&amp;rsquo;ll show you some cool demos from our research and tools we wrote for our creative assessments, demonstrating C&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;C &amp;ldquo;living of the land&amp;rdquo; with your email client, Bluetooth with text messages, SSIDs and even dropped packets ;-)</description></item><item><title>Volunteers</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/volunteers/</guid><description> Volunteers Looking for a great opportunity to give back to our awesome community? Email us at volunteer@bsidestlv.com</description></item></channel></rss>