<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Closing words</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/closing_words/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:50:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/closing_words/</guid><description>Closing words</description></item><item><title>Cyber Cold War by Proxy: Saudi vs. Iran</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy__saudi_vs__iran/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy__saudi_vs__iran/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Cold War in the Middle East, Iran vs. Saudi Arabia &amp;amp; the entire region. The year 2012 almost crashed every world economy, threatening to bring the modern world to an end with the first Shamoon attacks by Iran. Since then, Iran has launched devastating cyber attacks against its perceived enemies involving critical infrastructure, to manipulate the oil markets in its favor. Join Chris on a journey of fighting near constant Cyberwar attacks and counter attacks!</description></item><item><title>CTF announcement</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/ctf_announcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:40:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/ctf_announcement/</guid><description>CTF announcement</description></item><item><title>Community Talk: Volunteering during crisis - The CTI League</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/community_talk___volunteering_during_crisis____the_cti_league/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:20:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/community_talk___volunteering_during_crisis____the_cti_league/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Volunteering during crisis - CTI League, a global threat intelligence experts community that neutralize cyber threats exploiting the current COVID-19 pandemic&amp;rdquo;. In the last months, a global army of 1800 cyber threat intelligence volunteers has been fighting threat actors looking to exploit the COVID-19 pandemic. The Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) League is the first community and global CERT in the world, established for helping the medical sector in its most sensitive time.</description></item><item><title>Break #3</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:10:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__3/</guid><description>10 minutes break - please visit our sponsors! https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/</description></item><item><title>Yoga Break with Emily</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/yoga_break_with_emily/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:55:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/yoga_break_with_emily/</guid><description>Stretch out and enjoy a short yoga practice with Emily Shain. Some easy yoga moves everyone can do at home! http://www.yogawemily.com/</description></item><item><title>Free Blue-Team TTPs: Stop Shiny Object Syndrome</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue_team_ttps__stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:10:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue_team_ttps__stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</guid><description>Too many blue-teamers get dazzled by hype for fancy new tools, especially those that are new to the industry. What they don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that there are free or cheap Tools, Tactics and Procedures that can shore up defenses today, without having to buy something new.</description></item><item><title>The Art of C2: Myths vs. Reality</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/the_art_of_c2__myths_vs__reality/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:50:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/the_art_of_c2__myths_vs__reality/</guid><description>“You need a TCP/IP connection for a C’n’C Server”, don&amp;rsquo;t you?? a dynamic, real-time Command and Control is not about an established connection. Nor TCP. or UDP. It’s a MINDSET :) We&amp;rsquo;ll show you some cool demos from our research and tools we wrote for our creative assessments, demonstrating C&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;C &amp;ldquo;living of the land&amp;rdquo; with your email client, Bluetooth with text messages, SSIDs and even dropped packets ;-)</description></item><item><title>Eliminating Alert Fatigue: Reducing False Positives Through Better Engineering</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue__reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue__reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</guid><description>False Positive alerts are the bane of blue teams everywhere. Countless hours are lost as Security Operation Center analysts attempt to separate the wheat from the alert chaff to find the real indicators of an attack. Reducing FPs is thus a critical goal for any security platform. Yet reducing FPs at the expense of missing the signs of an actual threat is inviting disaster. The solution to this conundrum lies in better engineering: building the right tools to accurately assess alerts at scale.</description></item><item><title>Break #2</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:15:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__2/</guid><description>10 minutes break</description></item><item><title>Shatter Reloaded: Reviving shatter attacks to escape sandboxes and evade endpoint security products</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded__reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded__reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</guid><description>Shatter attacks were all the rage in 2003 but were quickly neutralized by DEP, UIPI and Session 0 isolation. 15 years later, confronted with a commercial sandbox and with state-of-the-art endpoint security products – we brought Shatter attacks back to life, extending and weaponizing them to be useful once more. In this talk, we’ll present a novel code injection technique that uses an enhanced shatter attack to stealthily inject code into window explorer on Win7 &amp;amp; Win10.</description></item><item><title>Now You TCP Me, Now You Don't: The Strengths and Weaknesses of Various Internet Scanning Services</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me__now_you_don_t__the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me__now_you_don_t__the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</guid><description>A wild router is connected to the web! Are Shodan and Censys the only ones who index it? Absolutely not! They are only two of the many internet scanning services that let users interact with port scanning data they routinely collect. Although their names are well-known, details about them, the data they gather, and how best to use them are more word-of-mouth than common knowledge. I will explore these and other lesser-known websites, and help security researchers understand their strengths.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Break</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</guid><description>Lunch break</description></item><item><title>Panel - 'Security Careers in the Corona Age'</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel____security_careers_in_the_corona_age_/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:05:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel____security_careers_in_the_corona_age_/</guid><description>How has the world of work changed for security pros? What is the Covid Effect on jobs in our industry? Is now the time to go Freelance or Corp? How are community organizations like BSidesTLV, OWASP and Cyber Ladies helping out? These are some of the questions we will explore in this fun, fast paced panel!</description></item><item><title>Regipy: Automating registry forensics with python</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy__automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:35:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy__automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</guid><description>Regipy is an OS independent python library for parsing offline registry hives. Regipy can be used to parse registry hives in scale (collected from hundreds of machines) and a lot of interesting data analysis can be done on the results, as I intend to show in the Demo. The demo would be very practical and show how the results of Regipy can be useful to crack a forensic case. (See a small example in the blog post attached)</description></item><item><title>Break #1</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/break__1/</guid><description>10 minutes break</description></item><item><title>ROP - From Zero to Nation State In 25 Minutes</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop___from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop___from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</guid><description>“The only interesting answers are those which destroy the questions.” ― Susan Sontag
Roll up your sleeves and prepare for hands on demonstration of transforming a simple process injection into a new improved version of Stack Bombing that will evade most detection tools.
We will focus on building a ROP and take a &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; approach to process injection, continuously improving the same code to evade detection and mitigation techniques.</description></item><item><title>WhoAmI, anyway?</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami__anyway_/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami__anyway_/</guid><description>All InfoSec challenges today may be traced back to the design mindset of the Internet Protocol Suite in the late 60&amp;rsquo;s &amp;amp; early 70&amp;rsquo;s: non-repudiation, confidentiality, spoofing etc’ were Not in the design goals of TCP/IP. Decades after, we’re creatively &amp;amp; immensely manipulating time &amp;amp; space over the internet. Malware uses deception to evade defenses, defenders use deception to deter adversaries. Attribution of actions to entities becomes challenging than ever. So WhoAreWe, anyway?</description></item><item><title>Opening Words: BSidesTLV 2020 - Welcome to the New Normal!</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/opening_words__bsidestlv_2020____welcome_to_the_new_normal_/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/opening_words__bsidestlv_2020____welcome_to_the_new_normal_/</guid><description>Opening Words: BSidesTLV 2020 - Welcome to the New Normal!</description></item><item><title>2020 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2020/</guid><description>Last update: September 10, 2020 11:35
BSidesTLV 2020 CTF prizes are sponsored by https://HackTheBox.eu/ CTF starts in: var countDownDate = new Date("Jun 27, 2020 09:00:00").getTime(); var tick = function() { var now = new Date().getTime(); var distance = countDownDate - now; var days = Math.floor(distance / (1000 * 60 * 60 * 24)); var hours = Math.floor((distance % (1000 * 60 * 60 * 24)) / (1000 * 60 * 60)); var minutes = Math.</description></item><item><title>The BSidesTLV 2020 Call for Papers</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</guid><description>The 2020 edition of Security BSides in Israel, BSidesTLV 2020, will take place once again during Tel Aviv University’s Cyber Week, on Thursday, July 2.
BSidesTLV is a hands-on, community-organized hacking and security research event. This is the chance for you to share knowledge, ideas and demonstrate what you’ve been up to!
We encourage talk submissions by both newbies and veterans, from people passionate about security from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>2019 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2019/</guid><description>Last update: September 10, 2020 11:35
Hall of Fame 1st Place Dan (dm0n) 2nd Place JCTF 3rd Place EY (3rN357&amp;Y0un9) Honorable mention Adam D JCTF Team YaakovCohen88 Schtrudel Narcissus Moshe Wagner Israel Erlich Dvd848 Our Team Reut Menashe El Profesor (w/Nimrod)
The Lost Contract (w/Nimrod) Roei Sherman The Lost Award</description></item><item><title>Hiring Ground</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</guid><description>BSidesTLV 2019 Hiring Ground - 24.6 10:00-16:00 This is the first year we are doing our BSidesTLV “Hiring Ground”. We are doing our best to have a wonderful event, but please make allowances for any mistakes we might make. Our hope is that this part of the event will be focused on helping members of our community find their next positions, and connect them with potential employers.
Agenda The hiring ground will operate at the 24.</description></item><item><title>2018 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2018/</guid><description>Hall of Fame 1st Place reclass (Nir Lavi and Intel’s team) 2nd Place babyr00t (known also as dm0n) 3rd Place JCTF (@schturdel, @nmontag, @YaakovCohen88 and Israel Erlich) Honorable mention Adam Donenfeld Running a Fair Game This excerpt is from an incident that occured during the CTF.
Yesterday, June 9th at 18:26 we discovered that someone has shared the flag for one of our challenges on Pastebin.</description></item><item><title>2016 CTF</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/CTF/2016/</guid><description>At the 2016 CTF was hosted and sponsored by Cellebrite
github: cool story bro
if you have any writeups or more information, please let me know!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben_israel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben_israel/</guid><description>Even before she first logged on to a router, Adi has loved the internet. And after she found routers and smart devices she realized the power that non-end-devices held. Since then, she&amp;rsquo;s searched the web for interesting phenomena using all available resources. With five years of experience, she hopes to share some of her knowledge and help the cybersecurity community utilize the tools available to them.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/bsidestlv_2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/bsidestlv_2020/</guid><description>Enjoy the break and visit our sponsors! https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</guid><description>Chris Kubecka is the founder and CEO of HypaSec offering nation-state incident management, ethical hacking training in IT, IOT, ICS SCADA and expert advisory services to governments. Prior to HypaSec, she headed the Information Protection Group and international intelligence for the Aramco family. Re-establishing international business operations, helping to stabilize the oil market and implementing digital security after the company suffered from the world’s most devastating Shamoon cyberwarfare attacks which wiped out 85% of computer systems which deeply affected the countries of Saudi Arabia, Qatar and Bahrain.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</guid><description>Dana leads Security Research for Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft, researching and developing new cyber security threat detections. She started her career in an elite Israeli military cyber intelligence unit (&amp;lsquo;8200&amp;rsquo;), proceeded to work at a Big Data startup, and then joined Google, in its Zurich HQ. For the past 5 years she has been working on Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft. Dana is passionate about Operating Systems and Windows Internals.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</guid><description>Co-Founder of 10root Cyber security</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/emily_shain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/emily_shain/</guid><description>Emily Shain has a diverse yoga background, studying Ashtanga-Vinyasa in Israel, Elemental Yoga Therapy in Bali, Yin Yoga in Portugal and the Chakras in India. Since 2015, Emily has taught by bringing together these different schools of yogic wisdom to form a holistic, fluid and creative flow. http://www.yogawemily.com/
https://www.facebook.com/emyogatelaviv/
http://instagram.com/yogawithemily</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</guid><description>Gil Fidel is the Head of R&amp;amp;D at Accenture Security Israel (Maglan), with a long track of cutting-edge Research and Engineering in the fields of cyber security, windows internals, A/V streaming, network security &amp;amp; encryption, virtualization and AI/ML.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart_magen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart_magen/</guid><description>BSidesTLV Chairman and CTF Lead</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</guid><description>Keren Elazari is an internationally recognized security analyst, researcher, writer and speaker. Since 2000, Keren has worked with leading Israeli security firms, government organizations, big 4 and fortune 500 companies. Keren covers emerging security technologies as an independent strategic analyst and advisor. In 2014, Keren became the first Israeli woman to speak at the prestigious TED Conference. Keren’s talk has been viewed by millions, translated to 30 languages, and chosen for TED’s ‘Most Powerful Ideas’.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g__sthoeger_korman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g__sthoeger_korman/</guid><description>Currently working on the R&amp;amp;D team in Sygnia, working on new tools for the IR analysts in the company. Prior to that I worked in an incident response position in Sygnia for two years. Before joining Sygnia I worked at IBM&amp;rsquo;s Trusteer as a malware researcher reversing &amp;amp; analyzing financial malware. I did military service in the software division of the IAF (Israeli Airforce) for 6 years in multiple DFIR &amp;amp; IT positions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/ohad_zaidenberg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/ohad_zaidenberg/</guid><description>Ohad established the CTI League, a global cyber threat intelligence community spanning 76 countries, to neutralize cyber threats targeting the medical sector and exploiting the current COVID-19 pandemic. As well as being the founder of the CTI League, Ohad Zaidenberg is the Lead Cyber Intelligence Researcher for ClearSky Cyber Security, Israel. Prior to his role in ClearSky, Ohad was a commander in the IDF’s elite intelligence unit, Unit 8200. Ohad tracks state-sponsored and state-backed malware, propaganda, influence campaigns, and psychological warfare.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_cohen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_cohen/</guid><description>As an experienced Incident Response investigator and manager, Omer has a wealth of knowledge and experience in the areas of cyber security, security research, software development and system administration, as well as network architecture and design. Omer has delivered and implemented numerous projects involving cutting edge technologies for multiple security related applications in addition to providing accurate and appropriate information security consulting and incident response services to Fortune 500 companies and other leading organization.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</guid><description>Omer is End-Point team lead at Symantec (formerly Javelin Networks). His team focuses on methods to covertly manipulate OS internals. Before Symantec he was a malware researcher at IBM Trusteer for two years focusing on financial malware families. In the past he has worked at Algotec for six years developing medical imaging software and at IDF&amp;rsquo;s technology unit for three years as dev team lead. Omer lectured at DEF CON, DerbyCon, Virus Bulletin and Zero Nights conferences.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/reut_menashe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/reut_menashe/</guid><description>Founder of Tetrisponse, incident response expert. Leader of leading cyber ladies Executive producer bsidesTLV</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/robert_wagner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/robert_wagner/</guid><description>Robert Wagner is a security professional with 15+ years of InfoSec experience. He is a co-founder of “Hak4Kidz.com”, an organizer of BurbSecCon in Chicago, and is on the Board of Directors of the ISSA Chicago Chapter.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/roei_sherman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/roei_sherman/</guid><description>Experienced Senior Information Security Professional with a demonstrated history of working in the information security industry. Skilled in overall penetration testing, red team assessment, physical security and overall security posture improvements. Holding several security certifications.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</guid><description>Y1nTh35h3ll, InfoSec Researcher, White ^ haכk3r @ 10Root. Founder of the Oriental Rock Orchestra. P0w3r5h3ll dude. mother of Bouzoukitara (musical instrument). AD Protector.
Since the early 1990s, accumulated extensive experience in information security, adversary simulations/Red-Blue team training, conducting internal investigations and more. Worked for Microsoft ~8 years as Technology Group Manager and coded support tools for Windows Server. Advisory board @ Javelin Networks (sold to Symantec in 2018). Spoke at TED and TEDx events, and was awarded 4 Peace and friendship awards by cities and governments around the world.</description></item><item><title>AppsFlyer</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/appsflyer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/appsflyer/</guid><description>Check out AppsFlyer @ https://bsidestlv2020appsflyer.splashthat.com/</description></item><item><title>Check Point</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/checkpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/checkpoint/</guid><description>Check out Check Point Research @ https://research.checkpoint.com/</description></item><item><title>Clear Sky</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/clearsky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/clearsky/</guid><description>Check out Clear Sky @ https://www.clearskysec.com/</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>If you experience any inappropriate content or violation of our Code of Conduct during our events, you can contact us at report@bsidestlv.com
All attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at our conference are required to agree with the following code of conduct. Organizers will enforce this code throughout the event. We expect cooperation from all participants to help ensure a safe environment for everybody.
BSidesTLV is dedicated to providing a safe and harassment-free conference experience regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices, to all participants.</description></item><item><title>Cybereason</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cybereason/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cybereason/</guid><description>Check out Cybereason @ https://www.cybereason.com/cybereason-nerf-tlv</description></item><item><title>CyberWeek</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cyberweek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/cyberweek/</guid><description>Check out CyberWeek @ https://cyberweek.tau.ac.il/2020/</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/faq/</guid><description>What is Security BSides, anyway? Started by a group of hackers, security researchers and people passionate about cyber security, who are keen to share their knowledge and ideas, Security Bsides is a global network of community oriented, grassroots non-profit security events taking place anywhere from Athens, to São Paulo!
From the Bsides Community Wiki: “Bsides creates opportunities for individuals to both present and participate in an intimate atmosphere that encourages collaboration.</description></item><item><title>HackerOne</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/hackerone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/hackerone/</guid><description>Check out HackerOne @ https://hackerone.com/sign_up</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/htb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/htb/</guid><description>Check out HackTheBox @ https://www.hackthebox.eu/</description></item><item><title>ICRC</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/icrc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/icrc/</guid><description>Check out ICRC @ https://icrc.tau.ac.il/</description></item><item><title>Intel</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/intel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/intel/</guid><description>Check out Intel @ https://www.intel.co.il/content/www/il/he/homepage.html</description></item><item><title>Neuralegion</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/neuralegion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/sponsors/neuralegion/</guid><description>Check out Neuralegion @ https://go.neuralegion.com/bsidestlv</description></item><item><title>Volunteers</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/volunteers/</guid><description> Volunteers Looking for a great opportunity to give back to our awesome community? Email us at volunteer@bsidestlv.com</description></item></channel></rss>