<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speakers on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/</link><description>Recent content in Speakers on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben-israel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/adi_ben-israel/</guid><description>Even before she first logged on to a router, Adi has loved the internet. And after she found routers and smart devices she realized the power that non-end-devices held. Since then, she&amp;rsquo;s searched the web for interesting phenomena using all available resources. With five years of experience, she hopes to share some of her knowledge and help the cybersecurity community utilize the tools available to them.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/chris_kubecka/</guid><description>Chris Kubecka is the founder and CEO of HypaSec offering nation-state incident management, ethical hacking training in IT, IOT, ICS SCADA and expert advisory services to governments. Prior to HypaSec, she headed the Information Protection Group and international intelligence for the Aramco family. Re-establishing international business operations, helping to stabilize the oil market and implementing digital security after the company suffered from the world’s most devastating Shamoon cyberwarfare attacks which wiped out 85% of computer systems which deeply affected the countries of Saudi Arabia, Qatar and Bahrain.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dana_baril/</guid><description>Dana leads Security Research for Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft, researching and developing new cyber security threat detections. She started her career in an elite Israeli military cyber intelligence unit (&amp;lsquo;8200&amp;rsquo;), proceeded to work at a Big Data startup, and then joined Google, in its Zurich HQ. For the past 5 years she has been working on Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection at Microsoft. Dana is passionate about Operating Systems and Windows Internals.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/dor_amit/</guid><description>Co-Founder of 10root Cyber security</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/gil_fidel/</guid><description>Gil Fidel is the Head of R&amp;amp;D at Accenture Security Israel (Maglan), with a long track of cutting-edge Research and Engineering in the fields of cyber security, windows internals, A/V streaming, network security &amp;amp; encryption, virtualization and AI/ML.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart-magen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/guy_barnhart-magen/</guid><description>none</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/keren_elazari/</guid><description>Keren Elazari is an internationally recognized security analyst, researcher, writer and speaker. Since 2000, Keren has worked with leading Israeli security firms, government organizations, big 4 and fortune 500 companies. Keren covers emerging security technologies as an independent strategic analyst and advisor. In 2014, Keren became the first Israeli woman to speak at the prestigious TED Conference. Keren’s talk has been viewed by millions, translated to 30 languages, and chosen for TED’s ‘Most Powerful Ideas’.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g._sthoeger_korman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/martin_g._sthoeger_korman/</guid><description>Currently working on the R&amp;amp;D team in Sygnia, working on new tools for the IR analysts in the company. Prior to that I worked in an incident response position in Sygnia for two years. Before joining Sygnia I worked at IBM&amp;rsquo;s Trusteer as a malware researcher reversing &amp;amp; analyzing financial malware. I did military service in the software division of the IAF (Israeli Airforce) for 6 years in multiple DFIR &amp;amp; IT positions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/ohad_zaidenberg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/ohad_zaidenberg/</guid><description>null</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/omer_yair/</guid><description>Omer is End-Point team lead at Symantec (formerly Javelin Networks). His team focuses on methods to covertly manipulate OS internals. Before Symantec he was a malware researcher at IBM Trusteer for two years focusing on financial malware families. In the past he has worked at Algotec for six years developing medical imaging software and at IDF&amp;rsquo;s technology unit for three years as dev team lead. Omer lectured at DEF CON, DerbyCon, Virus Bulletin and Zero Nights conferences.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/speakers/yossi_sassi/</guid><description>Y1nTh35h3ll, InfoSec Researcher, White ^ haכk3r @ 10Root. Founder of the Oriental Rock Orchestra. P0w3r5h3ll dude. mother of Bouzoukitara (musical instrument). AD Protector.
Since the early 1990s, accumulated extensive experience in information security, adversary simulations/Red-Blue team training, conducting internal investigations and more. Worked for Microsoft ~8 years as Technology Group Manager and coded support tools for Windows Server. Advisory board @ Javelin Networks (sold to Symantec in 2018). Spoke at TED and TEDx events, and was awarded 4 Peace and friendship awards by cities and governments around the world.</description></item></channel></rss>