<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deep-dive technical on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/tags/Deep-dive-technical/</link><description>Recent content in Deep-dive technical on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/tags/Deep-dive-technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Cold War by Proxy: Saudi vs. Iran</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/cyber_cold_war_by_proxy_saudi_vs._iran/</guid><description>Welcome to the new Cold War in the Middle East, Iran vs. Saudi Arabia &amp;amp; the entire region. The year 2012 almost crashed every world economy, threatening to bring the modern world to an end with the first Shamoon attacks by Iran. Since nearly bring the world to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, Iran has launched devastating cyber attacks against it&amp;rsquo;s perceived enemies involving critical infrastructure, to manipulate the oil markets in its favor.</description></item><item><title>Free Blue-Team TTPs: Stop Shiny Object Syndrome</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue-team_ttps_stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:10:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/free_blue-team_ttps_stop_shiny_object_syndrome/</guid><description>Too many blue-teamers get dazzled by hype for fancy new tools, especially those that are new to the industry. What they don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that there are free or cheap Tools, Tactics and Procedures that can shore up defenses today, without having to buy something new.</description></item><item><title>Shatter Reloaded: Reviving shatter attacks to escape sandboxes and evade endpoint security products</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/shatter_reloaded_reviving_shatter_attacks_to_escape_sandboxes_and_evade_endpoint_security_products/</guid><description>Shatter attacks were all the rage in 2003 but were quickly neutralized by DEP, UIPI and Session 0 isolation. 15 years later, confronted with a commercial sandbox and with state-of-the-art endpoint security products – we brought Shatter attacks back to life, extending and weaponizing them to be useful once more. In this talk, we’ll present a novel code injection technique that uses an enhanced shatter attack to stealthily inject code into window explorer on Win7 &amp;amp; Win10.</description></item></channel></rss>