<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regular Talk on BSidesTLV 2020</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/tags/Regular-Talk/</link><description>Recent content in Regular Talk on BSidesTLV 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:25:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/tags/Regular-Talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eliminating Alert Fatigue: Reducing False Positives Through Better Engineering</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 15:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/eliminating_alert_fatigue_reducing_false_positives_through_better_engineering/</guid><description>False Positive alerts are the bane of blue teams everywhere. Countless hours are lost as Security Operation Center analysts attempt to separate the wheat from the alert chaff to find the real indicators of an attack. Reducing FPs is thus a critical goal for any security platform. Yet reducing FPs at the expense of missing the signs of an actual threat is inviting disaster. The solution to this conundrum lies in better engineering: building the right tools to accurately assess alerts at scale.</description></item><item><title>Now You TCP Me, Now You Don't: The Strengths and Weaknesses of Various Internet Scanning Services</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/now_you_tcp_me_now_you_dont_the_strengths_and_weaknesses_of_various_internet_scanning_services/</guid><description>A wild router is connected to the web! Are Shodan and Censys the only ones who index it? Absolutely not! They are only two of the many internet scanning services that let users interact with port scanning data they routinely collect. Although their names are well-known, details about them, the data they gather, and how best to use them are more word-of-mouth than common knowledge. I will explore these and other lesser-known websites, and help security researchers understand their strengths.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Break</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/lunch_break/</guid><description>Lunch break</description></item><item><title>Regipy: Automating registry forensics with python</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:05:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/regipy_automating_registry_forensics_with_python/</guid><description>Regipy is an OS independent python library for parsing offline registry hives. Regipy can be used to parse registry hives in scale (collected from hundreds of machines) and a lot of interesting data analysis can be done on the results, as I intend to show in the Demo. The demo would be very practical and show how the results of Regipy can be useful to crack a forensic case. (See a small example in the blog post attached)</description></item><item><title>Panel - 'Security Careers in the Corona Age' with Reut Menashe Avi Douglen</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel_-_security_careers_in_the_corona_age_with_reut_menashe_avi_douglen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:30:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/panel_-_security_careers_in_the_corona_age_with_reut_menashe_avi_douglen/</guid><description>TBD</description></item><item><title>ROP - From Zero to Nation State In 25 Minutes</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/rop_-_from_zero_to_nation_state_in_25_minutes/</guid><description>“The only interesting answers are those which destroy the questions.” ― Susan Sontag
Roll up your sleeves and prepare for hands on demonstration of transforming a simple process injection into a new improved version of Stack Bombing that will evade most detection tools.
We will focus on building a ROP and take a &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; approach to process injection, continuously improving the same code to evade detection and mitigation techniques.</description></item><item><title>WhoAmI, anyway?</title><link>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami_anyway/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:25:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bsidestlv.com/agenda/whoami_anyway/</guid><description>All InfoSec challenges today may be traced back to the design mindset of the Internet Protocol Suite in the late 60&amp;rsquo;s &amp;amp; early 70&amp;rsquo;s: non-repudiation, confidentiality, spoofing etc’ were Not in the design goals of TCP/IP. Decades after, we’re creatively &amp;amp; immensely manipulating time &amp;amp; space over the internet. Malware uses deception to evade defenses, defenders use deception to deter adversaries. Attribution of actions to entities becomes challenging than ever. So WhoAreWe, anyway?</description></item></channel></rss>